Hello everyone!
This is Osumi Tsuki from Miyagi Call Joy!
This is the 5th Miyagi Ramen Club!
Thank you very much!
The ramen boy who came to our memorable 5th edition is Kanaka!
Come here, come here.
I'm Mai Takahashi from Mirror Equal Joy. Pleased to meet you.
It's her first appearance.
Yes, it's my first time. Thank you very much.
We usually go out for ramen together, so I'm really happy to be here.
Here's the restaurant Mai and I are going to today!
Jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan jjan
What?
Wow!
Otsamai!
Ready?
Huh?
Come on, come on, come on!
Here we go.
Let's go, okay?
Let's go if we can.
Seino
Ramen noodles from Senregan...
Wow.
Not at all.
Right!
Jiro-style brick.
You've always wanted to go there.
First time.
Ramen is my first Jiro-style ramen.
I'm so glad.
Shall we go right away?
I'm going.
Shall we go?
Let's go!
So, I'm here in the store.
I'd like to buy a direct ticket now.
What do you think is good?
Is this pork and egg ramen the standard?
That's right!
Pork and egg, and this...
I'm curious about this one.
Sukiyaki
Um...
We've done a lot of prep work.
We've both done a lot of prep work.
Ramen and sukiyaki.
I'll go buy some.
I'll take it.
Half the noodles, please.
Half.
Yes, please.
I'll have half the amount of noodles, please.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm putting a pause on today.
I'm so nervous.
I've been watching youtube on Suslo TV before I came here today.
I've been watching every youtube video of people who've been to Sendai Bay.
I'm Yoshiozoe.
Jiro Ramen Maicchan's request came in.
For the debut of MILJER'S!
Cat's Clothing Woman's Channel on the album.
Winner!
He said he'll make it happen.
That's it!
I've made a request and it's come true!
It's a project that came true!
Yay! Thank you so much!
I'm so happy! It's my first Jiro Ramen too!
Really?
It's my first time.
But you and Micchan go out for all kinds of ramen, don't you?
Even in private?
That's right.
Before the music video.
We went out for ramen together.
It was pretty late.
We ate and it was a bit...
It was a sinful time.
Yes, it was a sinful time.
The next day's music video was really good, wasn't it?
It's the best music video I've ever seen.
I think it might have been my best music video.
I looked the cutest in the whole thing.
Before the music video.
It's a good idea to eat ramen the day before a big day
I might as well eat ramen the day before the music video.
That would be great...!
I think I'll keep doing it.
Before what music video?
Yumemiru Idol
They eat so much garlic before such a cute song.
They both ate fried rice too.
They cupped fried rice and kimchi together to make kim fried rice.
And I was like, "Oh, no, this is not good.
The next day I thought it was going to go well, and it went surprisingly well.
They both looked so cute.
I leaked.
There are a lot of girls who like Miyagi ramen.
So many.
Mugiko's pretty good.
She says she's a ramen lover, but she's still not in the ramen club.
Riko told me.
I thought I was the Jiro type. Riko told me.
But I made it because I requested it beforehand.
So you can have tsukemen.
Let's go private, Riko.
Okay, I'll go with you.
I'm not in the ramen club.
It's been a while.
Really?
I've been five times.
Once or twice in Tokyo, and the third time in Osaka.
Oh, it's nice to have that.
Gerna Rahmenation and the 4th one was at Okazuki's Manpukuya.
The fourth time I went to Okazuki's Manpukuya.
I finally came back.
Eh, finally came back
Giro-kei
I'm so glad I did, really.
I bought it for you.
You know...
I've got that one. It's called "Giro".
The call, you know, it's hard to make.
This one, right here.
This is it.
If you want more vegetables, add more vegetables.
Ramen noodles, deep-fried noodles, and so on...
When I watched Miria's video, I saw that fried chicken is one of Chigirimoto's specialties.
Do you want to practice?
Practice?
Okay, let's start with you.
You have a lot of number 12s, right?
Oh, you have a lot of number 12. You see, I have a lot of number 12 written down.
How would you like your meat, Mr. 12?
Garlic and oil, please.
Oh!
I'm so happy.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm only saying this because it's just the two of us.
I'm nervous to tell the waitress.
What if I bite?
What if I bite it and nothing gets through?
If I bite, I'll go blank.
I'm so nervous!
I'll be sukiyaki for you all!
Thank you very much.
Here it is.
Sukiyaki.
Do you think they'll sell it if I take a picture of it here?
Sukiyaki. The eggs are shining.
Green onions, egg, and some kind of bonito powder.
Looks so good! I've never had noodles with an egg before.
I've never had egg on noodles before. But have you?
Well, now that you mention it, it's a first.
But eggs go with everything. I'm looking forward to it.
Delicious.
Okay, so, guest number 11, do you want garlic?
Half a dozen veggies, some oil, and some fried chicken, please.
Wow.
I'm so nervous. I'm so nervous.
I thought it was Mai's, so I put the oil out.
I'm so nervous!
Half veggies and half oil with garlic, please.
Yes, ma'am.
First call in my life!
First call of my life!
You're glowing.
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, let's go.
I'll put the ramen on.
Ready, set, go!
Oh, no!
Sparkling!
I'm so happy!
Micchan...
This is half the vegetables
garlic, oil
fried tofu, and half noodles and
Sukiyaki!
That's amazing!
Fried chicken looks so delicious!
What about you, Mai-chan?
Mai-chan, let's see...
Garlic, half veggies, oil.
And sukiyaki!
I'm so happy!
That's great!
I can't wait to take a scythe bath!
The smell is amazing!
I can't wait to take a Sukiyaki bath!
Bon appétit!
Thank you very much.
Maine.
You're gonna lose your makeup.
It's here.
Happy, happy!
The noodles are so delicious!
They're so sticky!
I don't usually eat thick noodles.
It's so good in the soup!
I'm so happy!
Delicious!
I like the meat.
I love it!
I'll go back!
You should go.
Oh my god!
DISCOVERED
I'm going to have some of you. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Tallow. Tolololololol?
It's meat, but the moment I bit into it.
"whoop, whoop, whoop.
That's bad. That's bad. That's bad.
I'll have some of yours, too. Oh, there's some noodles.
Bon appétit. A little bit. Can you see it?
Isn't it good?
It's delicious.
Is it good?
I know.
I think I've changed my mind about that chashu pork. It's changing.
I see.
I definitely want everyone to come. I'm sure everyone's already here.
Yes, they are.
That's right. There were quite a lot of them.
This fried chicken is so delicious.
Do you want some?
That much?
It's more than I can eat.
Then, let's eat it. Where's Takahashi?
This way.
It's our first time since the beginning of April, but I'd like to go.
I'm so glad, because I was really interested in this place when I researched it beforehand.
Oh my God, I've taken so much. Is that okay? Yes, it's okay.
Let's put it in. Yes, great.
Look at this. It's amazing.
It looks too good. It looks too good.
Then, I'd like to try it. Bon appétit.
Oh no?
It's a little milder, it's kind of, you know, it's got a nice accent, it really changes the taste and it's delicious. It's really different and tasty.
You should try it, too, Micchan. Oh, well, I guess I'll give it a try.
Mmm, delicious.
Is it really round? Isn't it bad? It's so round.
The taste has changed. The taste has changed.
By dipping it in sukiyaki, it makes it go down your throat better. Slippery. It's so slippery.
Can I go ahead and eat it? Let's go ahead and eat. Let's go ahead and eat.
Oh, man, it's too good. I'm going to finish it.
So we both finished the meal.
Thank you for the food!
Thank you very much!
It was delicious!
The volume of the chashu pork was amazing!
The sukiyaki with different flavors was also very delicious!
Thank you very much!
I've learned a lot about ramen.
It has.
It's the first time I've used the word "expanded.
It was delicious!
Thank you very much.
Now that that's all said and done, I'd like to make the Ramen Club's annual Ramen Karuta.
We always start the karuta with the first letter of Jamaichi restaurant.
Senri Moto, so it's "back".
That's right.
That's the only way to say "back.
Speaking of backs... and speaking of Jiro type...
May I show you something, Mai-chan?
You want me to write it?
Yes, like this, like this.
And then, "chan-chan".
I've done my homework.
I'm so happy.
That's good.
I wrote your name.
Kanji?
Kanji.
Then you write it neatly and with a good pen.
That's great!
Write my kanji with a nice brush, too.
Yes, sir.
Finished!
It's done!
Now that it's done, I'd like to present it to you.
Here it is!
Ta-da!
Fatty oil and garlic are so good!
It was all delicious.
Fatty oil and garlic
I think the marshmashy one is Jiro's style
I chose this one.
It's so good!
It was really good!
If you liked the video, please subscribe to our channel and leave a comment.
If you liked the video, please subscribe to the channel, click the "Good" button, and leave a comment!
That's all for now, this is Mizuki Oshina and Mai Takahashi from Mairi Korzai!
Bye bye!